这是天堂
This is heaven.
真是天堂啊
This is absolute heaven.
你是说跟你未来老公共度一天吗
Yeah, you mean spending the day with your future husband?
不  不是啦
No, no. Not that.
不是
Not that?
不不  不止是这样
No, no, no. I mean, not only that.
都下午两点了
It's 2:00.
我还穿着睡衣
I'm in my P.J.S.
我们在看报纸
We're reading the newspapers.
我从没机会这样做
I never get to do this.
因为你从来不休假
Because you never take any time off.
我们只要无所事事就好
All we have to do is loaf around.
不用干活儿  只要一直浪费时间
There's no work, no goals other than to waste hours on end.
好了  别描述我的生活了
Okay. Stop describing my life.
不过有件事我们今天得完成
Though there is one thing we should get done today.
我们得给喜帖挑一款字体
We need to pick a font for our "save the date" cards.
真的吗  真要做这事
Really? We're gonna do that?
我们连场地都没有呢
We don't even have a venue yet.
截止期限能  鞭策我
Yeah. I find deadlines...inspiring.
这个怎么样
How about this one?
不要  镶边太多
No. It's too frilly.
同意
Agreed.
这个  太严肃了
And this -- ooh, this is...far too severe.
好像在说  你立马就得给我空出时间来
You will save the date now.
我喜欢这个  你呢
Oh, I like that one. You?
没什么感觉
Mm, I'm not really feeling it,
不过你可以说服我
though I guess, uh, you could convince me.
我肯定可以
I bet I could.
你可得花一番工夫
Yeah, I mean, you'd have to work pretty hard
我正准备这么做呢
Well, I'm prepared to do just that.
因为我很清楚咱俩目前需要的
Because it's clear to me that what we both need right now
就是一款非常棒的字体
is a really good font.
是的  太对了
Yes, we do. That's so true.
史上最差时机
And worst timing ever.
警探  你多久能到警局
Detective, how soon can you get here?
长官  我今天不当班
Uh, sir, I'm actually not on call today.
我知道  但出了点事
I'm aware of that, but something has come up,
恐怕等不了
and I'm afraid it can't wait.
我二十分钟后能到
Well, I can get there in 20 minutes.
还有一件事  一个人来
One more thing -- come alone.
别带上卡塞尔先生
Do not bring Mr. Castle.
是  长官
Uh...yes, sir.
盖茨找你什么事
So, what's Gates up to
除了妨碍我们的家庭欢愉
aside from sabotaging our domestic bliss?
不知道
I don't know.
但我得走了
But I got to go.
我大概不能说服你...
I don't suppose I could convince you to just --
不能
No.
没关系  不要紧
Yeah. Don't worry. It's fine.
别担心  我没事
Don't worry about it. I'm fine.
我就  写写东西吧
I'll just, uh -- I'll do some writing...
如果我能  集中精神的话
if I can... manage to focus.
贝克特  你不是休息呢吗
Yo, Beckett. I thought you were off.
刚刚那是副局长吗
Was that the deputy commissioner?
是的  这儿的黄铜[高级警官]可比
Yeah, there's been more brass through here
-军乐队还多  -怎么回事
- than a marching band. - What's going on?
需者方知
It's all need-to-know,
-而咱俩不是  -但不管是怎么回事
- and we didn't make the list. - But whatever's happening
都在那间会议室讨论
is going down in that conference room.
警探
Detective.
-在  -在
- Yep. - Yep.
-贝克特  -不好意思
- Beckett. - Sorry.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett,
缉毒队警监富勒
Capton Fowler, head of narcotics.
谢谢你赶来  警探
Thank you for coming, detective.
我将要告诉你的事不能泄露
What I'm about to tell you cannot leave this room.
明白  长官
Yeah. Understood, sir.
这六名死者被人割喉
These six victims had their throats cut.
他们都是中高等级的毒贩
They were mid-to upper-level drug dealers.
两名是青少年
Two were teenagers.
他们都在过去几个月内遇害
They were all murdered in the past few months
这期间出现了一个新贩毒集团
when a new drug ring muscled in
抢走了住宅区那片的海洛因和可卡因买卖
and took over most of the uptown heroin and cocaine trade.
新贩毒集团
A new drug ring?
是谁
Well, who are they?
局长让我查明究竟
The commissioner asked me to find that out
一举缴获他们  但他们隐藏很深
and shut them down, but they're invisible, these guys.
他们不用银行  所以我们无法追踪金钱
They don't use banks, so we can't follow the money.
他们不让街头毒贩
They make sure their street dealers
见到供货人
never meet their suppliers.
所以抓到一个毒贩
So, when you bust a dealer,
他也不知道自己为谁做事
he doesn't know who he's working for.
正是
Exactly.
查了三个月  我们还是一无所获
So, three months in, and we have nothing.
除了拉兹拉斯  我们连一个名字都没查到
We don't even know any of their names, except for Lazarus.
-拉兹拉斯是谁  -他们的老大
- And who is Lazarus? - The leader.
当然不是真名
Not his real name, of course.
昨天  警方截取了一通电话
Then yesterday, a phone intercept
找到了这个女人  伊莲娜·马科夫
led us to this woman -- Elena Markov.
她坦白自己是那个集团中一个低级运毒人
She copped to being a low-level drug courier in the ring.
在俄罗斯出生  作为邮购新娘来了美国
Born in Russia, she came here as a mail-order bride,
跟丈夫离婚
divorced her husband.
英语说得比我们都好
She learned to speak English better than we do
靠做兼职翻译过活
and was getting by as a freelance translator.
她从没惹上过麻烦  直至今日
She'd never been in trouble before, at least not till now.
我在找工作  又听说了一条赚钱的门路
I needed work, and I heard about a way to make money.
只要打个电话就行  所以我做了
All I had to do was call a number, so I did.
一旦加入  就脱不了身了
But once I got in, I couldn't get out.
你在集团里的联系人是谁
Who was your contact in the ring?
我没有联系人
I didn't have one.
我会收到一条写明时间地点的短信
I would get a text with a time and a place,
然后得到一个内藏纸条的包裹
and I'd get a package with a note hidden inside
上面会告诉我送到哪去
that would tell me where to take it.
你见过谁吗
Did you ever, um, see anyone?
跟谁有过来往吗
Did you ever interact with anyone?
没有  一切都是匿名的
No. Everything was anonymous.
我不了解他们  他们也不了解我
I don't know them. They don't know me.
应该一直是那样的
It -- it needs to stay that way.
我只想回到我以前的生活
Look, I-I just want to get my life back.
线索看似是断了
It looked like another dead end.
结果今早  伊莲娜又收到贩毒集团的短信
Then this morning, Elena got another text from the ring.
这一回他们想见她  给她升职
This time, they wanted to meet her to offer her a promotion.
你们就有机会找出相关人员了
Which would give you guys a chance to get eyes on someone.
这是我们等待已久的突破口
It's the break we've been waiting for.
所以我们希望伊莲娜同意会面
So, we leveraged Elena to take the meet,
但她却想自杀
but she tried to commit suicide.
她现在在警方的严密监管下
She's in intensive care under police guard.
长官  很遗憾听到这些
Sir, I'm sorry to hear about that,
但这些跟我有什么关系
but what does this all have to do with me?
会面安排在今天五点
The meeting is set for 5:00 today,
而且不会再有第二次这种机会了
and a chance like this is not gonna come back around,
我们在纽约警察中筛选了跟伊莲娜年龄相仿
so we combed the NYPD database for someone about Elena's age
相貌相似  掌握流利俄语的人
and appearance who speaks fluent Russian,
以防万一
in case that's relevant.
只跳出了一个名字  那就是你
Only one name came up -- yours.
你要我代替她去会面
You want me to go in her place?
去韦德马克酒店
To the Widmark.
现个身  见见联络人  回来
Show up, meet your contact, and leave.
很快的
In and out.
如果他们发现你们替换了伊莲娜
What if they found out that you turned Elena
一切都是陷阱怎么办
and that this is all a trap?
那他们就不会约在韦德马克酒店见面
Then they wouldn't be meeting at the Widmark Hotel.
我们行事非常小心
We were very careful.
没人知道她联络了我们
No one knows she's made contact with us.
他们也有可能看到贝克特探长后
Still, there's the risk that they could see detective Beckett
认出她不是伊莲娜
and realize that she's not Elena.
短信中  他们让伊莲娜戴上红围巾
In the text, they asked Elena to wear a red scarf,
说明他们不知道她的长相
which tells us that they don't know her on sight.
我的人会在暗处观察你们的一举一动
My people will be in place watching every move you make.
我们还可以给你装上监听器  如果你愿意
We can even fit you with a monitored mike, if you like.
我...
I...
探长  现在事关重大
Detective, something big is going on out there,
这是我们查案的最佳机会
and this is our best chance to find out what.
会面安排在两小时后  我需要你的答复
But the meeting's in two hours, so I need your answer.
援兵到
Reinforcements.
卡塞尔
Castle.
听起来你的完成了不少写作啊
Wow. You sound like you are getting a lot of writing done.
都怪你
I blame you for that.
你什么时候回来
When are you coming back?
我不知道  几小时后吧
Uh, I don't know. A couple hours?
我有个会
I have a meeting.
别问我是什么会
A-and don't ask me what it is.
那我就偏要问了
Well, now I have to ask.
我得出发了
It...look, I-I have to get going.
回来能赶上晚饭
I should be back in time for dinner.
或许我们能一起喝杯红酒
Maybe we can have a glass of wine together.
我会把酒醒到完美状态的
I will decant something amazing.
好的  爱你  拜
Okay. I love you. Bye.
我得跟你说  我不在乎
I have to tell you I don't care
富勒警监强买强卖的那套
for captain Fowler's hard-sell tactics.
这是毒品案件
This is a narcotics operation.
这不关你的事
It's not your problem,
你可以拒绝  我承担压力
so you can walk away and I'll take the heat.
谢谢你  长官  但我能搞定
Thank you, sir, but I-I can handle this.
那他们准备再过一遍计划
Then they're ready to review the plan
然后给你个最后指示
and give you a final briefing.
记住  不要像警察那样行事
Remember, don't move like a cop.
你就是伊莲娜  你害怕他们
You're Elena. You're intimidated by these guys.
大堂里会有五个便衣警察
There will be five plainclothes officers in the lobby
酒店里遍布得更多
and more throughout the hotel.
搭北面的电梯  上11楼
Head to the north elevator and go to the 11th floor.
见面房间是1123
The meet is in room 1123.
楼上的卧底警官会支援你
Undercover officers up there will have your back.
保持冷静  记住所有见过的名字和脸
Stay calm, memorize names and faces of whomever you meet,
然后马上出来
and you'll be out in no time.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
去几楼
Which floor?
11.
好的
Okay.
不许动
Don't move a muscle.
电梯到达11楼了
Elevator just got to 11.
是空的
It's empty.
我是凯特·贝克特探长
This is detective Kate Beckett.
如果听得见我说话  我被绑架了
If you can hear me, I've been abducted.
我在一辆白色货车里  纽约牌照
I'm in a white cube van, New York plates.
我们已经开了大约20分钟了
We've been traveling for about 20 minutes.
车拐了很多弯
We've been making a lot of turns,
但好像是开往东边
but I think we're headed east.
富勒警监  你能听到我说话吗
Captain Fowler, if you can hear me,
这已经严重破坏了我的晚餐计划
this is seriously ruining my dinner plans.
你向我保证你会照看好她
You promised me that you had her back.
怎么回事
What happened?
我们安排了个简单的会面
We were set up for a simple meet,
而不是有预谋的绑架
not an orchestrated kidnapping.
监控录像有没有拍到是谁干的
The security cameras -- did they get a shot of who did this?
整个酒店的监控录像都被暂时切断了
They were disabled momentarily throughout the hotel.
那贝克特身上装的窃听器呢
What about the mike Beckett had on?
她进了电梯之后我们就停止接收了
We stopped receiving audio after she got in the elevator.
信号在封闭的环境里强度下降
The signal strength drops in enclosed spaces.
让我猜猜
And let me guess --
住在1123号房的人根本不知道见面的事
Whoever was in room 1123 didn't know about a meeting
因为根本就没安排见面
because there never was gonna be one.
我们已经发布了限制警报
Look, we've issued a limited alert.
限制警报
Limited alert?!
我们得请求武装部队的支援
We need to call in the Cavalry here.
我们清楚贩毒集团追踪警方的无线通讯
We know the drug ring tracks police radios.
发送信号会让形势变得更糟
Sending up a flare could make things worse.
他们肯定知道了你那个线人交待了实情
They must have known that your girl rolled on them,
或者发现贝克特是警察
or they made Beckett.
总之  如果我们不马上找她的话她就会死的
Either way, she's dead if we don't find her immediately.
先生们  发生了点状况
Gentlemen, we have a situation.
车已经行走了大约一个小时  也许不止
We've been driving for about an hour now, maybe more.
双行车道  车流量不是很多
Uh, two-lane road, not a lot of traffic, um...
减速了
We're slowing down.
车停下来了
We've stopped.
我得把窃听器扔掉了
I've got to get rid of this thing.
双膝跪地  脸面向驾驶室墙面
Get on your knees and face the wall toward the cab.
不许动
Do not move.
别转身
Don't turn around.
现在看看你身上有没有窃听器
Time to see if you're wearing a wire.
我身上没窃听器
I'm not wearing a wire.
一会儿就知道了
Yeah, we'll see about that.
我是凯特·贝克特探长
This is Detective Kate Beckett.
我现在没空接你电话  请留言
I'm unavailable at the moment, but please leave a message.
我知道你今晚和凯瑟琳有计划
Well, I know you have plans with Katherine this evening,
我就识趣地不当电灯泡了
so I'm going to make myself scarce.
很好
Oh, very nice.
我要去参加《布里顿海滩》的重演
I'm off to a revival of "Brighton Beach Memoirs."
祝我好运吧
Ha. Pray for me.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我联系不上贝克特
I-I can't get ahold of Beckett.
我给她发了短信  留言
I texted her. I left messages.
这不像她
This isn't like her.
也许她在分局有事走不开
Maybe she got tied up at the precinct.
你联系过莱恩和埃斯波西托了吗
Have you tried Ryan or Esposito?
我都打了  都直接转到留言信箱了
I called them both -- just go straight to voicemail.
我就觉得  有点不对劲
Just... something is not right.
现在要做什么
So, what happens now?
不是我说了算
It's not my call.
我们是在等他吗
Is that who we're waiting for?
那房间里的人
They're in that room?
你听上去很担心
You sound worried.
我该担心吗
Should I be?
你为什么这么特别
What the hell makes you so special?
我不特别
I'm not special.
我什么也不知道  我只负责转移包裹
I don't know anything. I just move packages.
我不构成威胁
I'm not a threat to anyone.
别再演戏了
You can just drop the act.
走吧  该你了
Let's go. You're up.
你是伊莲娜·马科夫
You are Elena Markov?
是的
Yes.
很高兴终于见到你
It's good to finally meet you.
你可以叫我琼斯先生  这位是海登先生
You can call me Mr. Jones, and this is Mr. Harden.
很抱歉见个面这么大费周章的
I'm sorry for the lengths we go to to have a meeting,
但是时代就是如此
but these are the times we live in.
需要点什么  喝酒吗
Uh, can I get you anything? A drink?
不用  谢谢
No. Thank you.
很好  那就谈正事
Good. To business, then.
你要知道我们有多重视你的服务
You should know how much we value your services,
尤其是拉兹拉斯
Lazarus in particular.
我尽我所能
Well, I do the best I can.
但一直是作为兼职
But always as a freelancer.
我们想要给你一个固定的职位
What we want to do is offer you a permanent position
为我们组织做事
with our organization.
当然了  这是周薪
That's per week, of course.
你觉得怎么样
How does that strike you?
出价很大方
It's very generous.
但是我要见拉兹拉斯一面
But I'm gonna need to meet Lazarus.
这可不行
That's not an option.
我得知道我在和谁做买卖
I need to know who I'm doing business with.
事关信任
It's a matter of trust.
好吧  我会向上级报告你的要求
All right. I'll pass along the request,
但得到答复之前你必须留在这儿
but you'll remain our guest here until I get an answer.
找间房让马科夫女士入住
Please see Miss Markov to a bedroom.
能和你说句话吗
Sir, can I have a word, please?
好  失陪一会儿
Sure. Would you excuse me, please?
-有什么事  -她有问题
- What's the problem? - She's the problem.
她完全不对劲
She's all wrong.
我一直在观察她
Look, I've been watching her.
她一副不知道为什么会来这儿的样子
She acted like she didn't know why she was here.
-埃斯波西托  -哈维  是我
- Esposito. - Javi, Javi, it's me.
贝克特  你在哪
Beckett, where are you?
一半警队都出动找你呢  大家快来
We've got half the force looking for you. Hey!
听着  追踪这通电话找到我
No. Listen. Get a trace on this phone. Get eyes on me.
我不知道我在哪  伊莲娜·马科夫是谁
I don't know where I am or who the hell Elena Markov is,
但她没讲实话
but her story is a lie.
她不只是底层运毒人
She is more than just a low-level courier.
你向来不喜欢我们招的新人
You never like it when we bring new people in,
特别是职位高于你的新人
especially above you.
不是  这次不是这么回事
That's not what it is, not this time.
她很害怕
Okay, she was afraid.
好  你就留心着她
All right, you keep an eye on her,
如果她真有问题  那你来解决她
And if she is wrong, then you get to do the honors, okay?
走吧
Let's go.
你是说我们追踪不了贝克特的电话吗
Are you telling me that we can't trace Beckett's call?
这是网络语音电话  通过匿名服务器连接
It's a voice-over-internet line fed through an anonymizer.
好吧  但我们总可以缩小范围吧
Okay, but can we at least narrow it down
缩小到打电话的区域
to the area where the call was made?
不行  信号通过乌克兰
No, it was routed through the Ukraine,
又经由欧洲各地
bounced all over Europe.
这些人做足了安全措施
These guys know security.
警监  为什么贝克特说
Captain, why did Beckett tell us
伊莲娜·马科夫不仅仅是个运毒人
that Elena Markov was more than just a courier?
我也不清楚
I have no idea.
那么你没有对我们隐瞒有关她的事咯
So, there's nothing about her that you haven't told us?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
她所讲的事情都证实了  但是
Every part of her story checked out, but...
什么
But what?
我们没有时间深入查证
We didn't have enough time to go deep,
事态进展得太快了
not with things moving this fast.
我们昨天才知道马科夫女士的事
We didn't even know Miss Markov until yesterday.
也许你根本不了解她
Well, maybe you didn't know her at all.
我们可以去弥补这点
Looks like we can fix that.
医院刚打来电话说她醒了
The hospital just called. She's conscious.
去审问她  查清事情的来龙去脉
Go talk to her. Get to the bottom of this.
我和你一起去  她认识我
I'll go with you. She knows me.
你们都没有回复我的电话
Hey, you guys have not been returning my calls.
贝克特在哪
Where's Beckett?
卡塞尔先生  去我办公室谈吧
Mr. Castle, why don't you come into my office?
赶快  跟上
Hurry it up! Quickly.
过来  往前走  这个方向
Over here. Let's go. Come here.
我们知道她在哪吗
Do we have any idea where she is?
交通监控录像拍到了一辆白色货车
Traffic-cam footage caught a white van
在她被绑架时驶离韦德马克酒店
heading away from the widmark right when she was abducted.
我们认为她在里头  也在尽力追查那辆车
We think she was in it, and we're trying to track it down.
还是有希望的
There are reasons for hope here.
愿闻其详
I'd love to hear them.
首先  他们没有认出她是警察
First of all, they didn't make her as a cop.
以为她是伊莲娜·马科夫  这就争取了时间
They think she's Elena Markov, which buys us time.
她假装成伊莲娜
She's pretending to be Elena
但她根本不知道伊莲娜是谁
when she doesn't know who Elena is?
她不可能永远不露馅的
She can't keep that up forever.
希望我们在露馅之前找到她
Well, hopefully, she won't have to.
只要伊莲娜告诉我们她知道的一切
Once Elena tells us everything that she knows about this,
就能顺藤摸瓜找到贝克特
it could lead us to Beckett.
大概一小时前马科夫女士苏醒了
Miss markov regained consciousness about an hour ago.
她情况稳定  所以我们把她移出了特护病房
She's stable, so we transferred her out of ICU.
她说什么了吗
Has she said anything yet?
只说活着真好
Just that she's glad to be alive.
她是清醒的吗
So, she's lucid?
是  但她遭遇这些痛苦后非常虚弱
Yes, but she's also extremely weak from her ordeal,
所以你们必须缩短审问时间
so, please, I'd ask that you limit your time with her
越短越好
as much as possible.
我们要得到答案  花再多时间也要审问到底
We need answers, so we're gonna question her as long as it takes.
就在前面  3410病房
Room's just up here -- 3410.
我以为你派了警员看守她
I thought you had an officer guarding her.
是的  他肯定在里头
We do. He must be inside with her.
伊莲娜·马科夫  纽约警察
Elena Markov, NYP--
妈的
Son of a bitch.
有警员受伤  警员受伤
We have an officer down! Officer down!
伊莲娜不见了
Elena's gone.
要么她杀了他逃了
Either she killed him and fled...
或者别人杀了他带走了她
Or someone else did and they grabbed her.
如果是他们带走了伊莲娜  那就是贝克特露馅了
If they took Elena, that means Beckett's cover's blown.
那她就死定了
She's as good as dead.
亲爱的里克
Dear Rick,
不知道我还有多少时间了
I don't know how much time I have,
说不定写这封信的时间也不够了
even to write this letter.
我知道的是  我已经被卷进来了
What I do know now is that I'm in this,
我活下来的唯一方法就是
and the only way I'm gonna make it out alive
把这个任务完成
is to see this through.
我知道大家都在找我
I'm sure everyone is looking for me,
如果他们知道我曾经在这里
and if they figure out I was here,
那鉴证组的人肯定会搜查这个房子
CSU's gonna search this house.
他们会搜寻血迹  那他们就会找到这个
They're gonna look for blood, and they will find it,
这样就能发现这封信了
which will lead them to this letter.
亲爱的  这是给你的信
Babe, it's your letter,
我希望你永远不用看这封信
and I hope you never have to read this --
因为我想亲口对你说这些
that I can tell you all of these things in person,
但假如我发生了什么不测
but if something happens and I don't make it,
我希望你知道  我们的合作关系
I need you to know that our partnership,
我们的恋情
our relationship
是上天赐予我最好的礼物
is the greatest thing that has ever happened to me.
你是个非常棒的人
You're an amazing man,
我爱你  全心全意
and I love you with all of my heart.
直到永远
Always.
琼斯先生有话和你说
Mr. Jones wants a word.
进来吧
Let's go.
我有个令人意外的消息
I've got surprising news.
拉兹拉斯同意见你了
Lazarus agreed to meet with you
不过你得先答应完成一项任务
if you agree to an assignment.
什么任务
What assignment?
等你完成了任务  你就能和他见面
You complete the assignment, you get the meeting.
要么接受  要么放弃
Take it or leave it.
成交  我需要做什么
Deal. What do I have to do?
你最擅长的事
What you do best.
杀掉他
Kill him.
要干净利落的
Make it clean.
我们到了
We're here.
这是哪里
Where's here?
你只要知道目标就在这座房子里就行了
All you need to know is that the target's in that house.
他一个人吗
Is he alone?
据我所知是的
As far as I know.
用这个
Use this.
拉兹拉斯不希望这个和你其他的任务联系起来
Lazarus doesn't want it to be connected to your other kills.
这人一定很重要吧  他是谁
Well, he's got to be important. Who is he?
他是名单上的下一个人
He's the next name on the list.
他做了什么
What does he do?
你怎么突然变得这么好奇了
Why are you so curious all of a sudden?
你没听说过调查吗
You ever hear of recon?
我做事之前喜欢先调查清楚
I like to know what I'm walking into.
他是不是警察  是不是毒品贩子
Is he a cop, is he a drug dealer,
这房子里有枪吗
Are there guns in the house?
好奇心让我活到现在
Curiosity keeps me alive.
他就是个普通人  无名小卒
The guy's a civilian, a nobody.
如果他是无名小卒  那为什么要杀他
If he's a nobody, then why are we killing him?
因为上头吩咐我们这么做
Because they told us to.
这里有什么问题吗
Look, is there -- is there a problem here?
有问题  我不是这样做事的
Yeah, there's a problem. I don't work like this.
我必须得了解清楚情况
I do my homework,
我要对情况有所掌控  这次太草率了
I control the variables, and this is sloppy.
也许拉兹拉斯想看看你随机应变的能力
You know, maybe Lazarus wanted to see how well you improvise.
也许  这也是我想看看的
You know, maybe I do, too.
好了  你到底是杀还是不杀
Now...are you gonna kill him or what?
你他妈的是谁
Who in the hell are you?!
办完了
It's done.
证明给我看
Show me.
什么
What?
不  我们没有时间了
No. We don't have time for this.
我说了  证明给我看
I said show me.
马上
Now.
正如我所说
Like I said.
我受够这种测试了
I'm done auditioning.
你告诉拉兹拉斯如果他再这么玩弄我
You tell Lazarus he wants to play games
交易就取消
and this deal's off.
好  我们回去吧
Yeah, we should get back.
刚又完成了一遍医院安保的检查
Just got off with the hospital security again.
整幢楼都封锁了
The building's locked down.
我们派人进去搜查了
We got teams going through,
不过至今没有发现伊莲娜的踪影
but there's no sign of Elena.
我们还是不知道这个女人到底是谁
And we still have no idea who this woman really is.
恐怕我们知道了
I'm afraid we do.
监控摄像头显示她是一个人离开的
Security video shows her leaving her room alone,
警官被割喉的方式
and the officer's throat was cut
和那些被割喉的毒贩子的方式完全一致
in the same exact manner as the murdered drug dealers --
角度吻合  都是左撇子  直奔颈动脉
Same angle, same left-handed stroke favoring the carotid.
那些短信所说的
That's what those text messages meant
关于包裹已被送达
about packages being delivered.
她根本不是贩毒组织的快递员
She wasn't a courier for the ring.
她是他们的雇佣杀手
She was their contract killer.
雇佣杀手
A contract killer?!
那是贝克特正在冒充的人
That's who Beckett is out there impersonating
你之前不知道
and you didn't know?
卡塞尔先生
Mr. Castle --
现在这个女人逍遥法外
And now this woman is out there somewhere?
你到底知不知道假如伊莲娜现身
Do you have any idea what's gonna happen to Beckett
贝克特会有多危险
when the real Elena shows up?
我们正在尽一切可能找到她
We're doing everything we can.
这还不够
Well, it's not enough.
冷静点
Hey, come on, man.
我是盖茨
This is Gates.
什么
What?
在哪
Where?
她让我趴下
She told me to get down on the floor,
然后告诉我她是警察
and then she said she was a cop
如果我想活命
and that if I wanted to live,
就必须严格按照她说的做
I had to do exactly what she said.
然后她去了厨房  拿了番茄酱
And then she went to the kitchen and she came back with ketchup
还  还  还有甜菜汁  然后
and -- and -- and beet juice and --
然后她让我躺着  尽可能的不动
and she told me to lie as still as possible
同时屏住呼吸
and to hold my breath.
波特先生
Mr. Potter,
她有提过任何她在哪
did she say anything else about where she was,
他们把她关在哪的信息吗
where they were keeping her?
有  她说是个院子
Yeah. She said it was some kind of a compound.
她不知道位置
She didn't know where
但她会努力尽快传消息出来
but that she would try to get a message out soon.
至少我们知道她还活着
At least we know she's still alive.
那个和她一起的家伙
This guy who was with her.
你看到他的脸了吗
Did you see his face?
没有  我埋着头
No. I had my head down.
你知道为什么贩毒集团
Do you have any idea why members of a drug ring
想要你的命吗
would want you dead?
不知道  那跟我风马牛不相及
No. That's not my world.
你是"泰波兰"事务所的律师
You're an attorney at Tyre, Potter, and Langston.
你主要经手哪种法律服务
What kind of law do you practice?
大部分是公司的
It's mostly corporate --
信托管理
trust administration.
你的工作涉及犯罪法吗
Do you do any criminal law?
不  从来没有
No, none.
我讨厌这种情况
I hate this.
她就在外面某个地方
She's out there somewhere,
身陷险境不自知
has no idea how much danger she's in,
而我却不能帮她
and I can't help her.
对  你不能
No, you can't.
但我们说的可是贝克特
But this is beckett we're talking about.
她是你的未婚妻
She might be your fiancee,
但也是个非常棒的警察  不要小看她
but she's also a damn good cop, so don't sell her short.
她会想出办法让我们知道情况如何的
She'll figure out a way to let us know what's going on,
知道后  我们会把她救出来
and when she does, we'll get her out.
如果不够及时呢
What if it's not in time?
事情办得怎么样
So, how did it go?
包裹寄到  毫无差错
The package was delivered without any issues.
很好
Good.
去洗把脸
Clean yourself up.
拉兹拉斯要见你
Lazarus wants to see you.
你会离开这里的  活着
You're getting out of here -- alive.
对不起  我真的要撒尿
Sorry. I really have to pee.
你介意吗
Do you mind?
不  没什么
No, it's fine.
多谢
Thank you.
演出棒极了  是吧
Great gig, huh?
是  惊呆了
Yeah, it's amazing.
我不知道这些家伙是谁
I don't know who these guys are,
但他们出手真阔绰
but they sure like to spend money.
快点儿  他等着呢
Come on. He's waiting.
这边
This way.
你让他待在地下室吗
You keep him in the basement?
他喜欢那儿
He likes it there.
他觉得那儿很适合他
He thinks it suits him.
你先请
After you.
怎么了
What's the matter?
以前没见过会计室吗
You've never seen a counting room before?
见过
Yes.
但从没见过这种规模的
But never to this scale.
拉兹拉斯可是雄心勃勃
Lazarus is a man of enormous appetites.
不可思议  你们居然能瞒过联调局
I'm impressed you've been able to hide this from the feds.
冰山一角而已
You don't know the half of it.
在这儿等着
Wait here.
可以了  进来
He's ready. Come in.
抱歉耽搁了这么久
I apologize for the delay.
我得解决些业务上的事情
I had to resolve a business matter.
当然
Of course.
我不常这样做  像这样的见面
I don't usually do this -- meet like this.
但为你  我要破例一次
But for you, I'll make an exception.
我们的需求和你的技能
Between our needs and your skill set,
可是大有赚头的
this could be a very profitable arrangement.
我也这么想
I agree.
很好
Good.
那么  既然我们已经见面了
So, now that we've met,
为什么不让我们的合作正式一点呢
why don't we formalize our arrangement?
你不是伊莲娜
You are not Elena.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我认得你
I know you.
不  不  我不这样认为
No. No, I don't think you do.
不不不  我从来没有忘掉过一张脸
No, no, no. I never forget a face.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
哦  别  别  别
Oh, no, no, no.
她是警察吗
She is a cop?
12分局凶杀组的
Homicide out of the 12th.
上次我见你的时候
Last time I saw you,
你想要把我按在墙上
You tried to put me through a wall.
控诉我谋杀了你妈妈
Accused me of murdering your mama.
从她的表情看来  她记得我
And from the look on her face, she remembers me.
不是吗  警探
Don't you, Detective?
瓦肯·西蒙斯
Vulcan Simmons.
你就是拉兹拉斯
You're Lazarus?
伙计们  是她
Yo, guys. It's her.
是个不认识的号码发来的
It came in from an unknown number.
但这是她的警号  一定是她
But that's her badge number. It's got to be her.
地址是5
"Addr is 5."
她想告诉我们地址
She was trying to send an address.
看来她被打断了
Looks like she got cut off.
去查这个电话
Run that phone number.
找到它的主人  找出它在哪
Find out who owns it and find out where it is.
好
Right.
我们别再演戏了  警探
Let's do it without all this Kabuki theater, Detective.
多不雅啊
It's undignified.
把我想知道的告诉我
Tell me what I want to know,
我就让你死得体面些
and I'll give you a proper death
不用再经受这些脏乱的折磨
without all this messy suffering.
告诉我
Now...
你的任务是什么
...what was your mission
关于拉兹拉斯你们知道什么
and what do they know about Lazarus?
你想要不雅
Do you want undignified?
等着看我怎么收拾你吧
Then wait till you see what I do to you.
知道吗  你真的很像你妈妈
You know, you're just like your mama --
不属于这个世界  却要在这玩火
both playing in worlds where you don't belong.
你母亲付出了生命的代价
Your mother paid for it with her life.
你也会的
So will you.
不过首先
But first...
把我想知道的告诉我
...tell me what I want to know.
刚跟运营商联系了
Yo. Just got off with the carrier.
知道电话在哪了吗
Any idea whose phone it is?
是预付电话  无法确认持有者
It's a pre-paid. There's no way to identify the owner.
有线索了
I got a hit.
信号是从斯卡斯代尔的信号塔发出的
The signal originated from a tower in Scarsdale.
很好  能确定位置吗
Great. Can you lock on the location?
不行  那条信息只经过了一个信号塔
No. The message pinged off a single tower.
斯卡斯代尔  纽约
三角定位  失败
如果没有其他两个信号塔
Without a second or third tower,
就无法缩小范围
there's no way to narrow it down.
根据信号强度判断
Depending on signal strength,
它可以是从十英里半径范围内的
it could have originated anywhere
任何地方发出的
within this 10-mile radius.
这比海里捞针还难
It would be easier to find a needle in a haystack.
你能定位到电话的GPS吗
Can you ping the GPS?
关了  而且电话好像也关了
It's off, and it looks like the phone's off, as well.
抱歉  没有其他办法追踪了
I'm sorry. I've got no other way to trace it.
我已经尽力了
That's the best I can do.
我知道你的肺快炸了
I know your lungs are burning.
我能感受到你灵魂深处的恐慌
I can feel the panic in your soul.
你只想让这一切结束
All you want is for this to end.
我保证我会让这一切结束的
And I promise I will end it.
只要你把我想知道的告诉我
Just tell me what I want to know.
把这里清理干净
Scrub the place.
找块地把她埋了
Find a patch of dirt to put her in --
别让人找到她
somewhere where she won't be found.
我喜欢这片树林
I love these woods.
我爸爸以前常带我来打猎
My daddy used to take me hunting up here when I was a kid.
我花了好几天研究每块石头  每棵树
I spent days learning every rock, every tree,
还有所有可以藏身的地方
all the secret little places to hide.
这么多年来总能派上用场
Over the years, it's come in handy.
知道吗  你一走进那扇门
You know, I had you made
我就看穿你了
from the moment you walked through the door.
从你眼里就可以看出
I could see it in your eyes.
我想  这女人不可能是杀手
I thought, "No way this woman's a killer."
不可能
No.
你不会想杀我的  海登
You don't want to kill me, Harden.
你知道我是警察
You know that I'm a cop.
我以前也杀过警察
Yeah, I've killed cops before.
事实上  其中一些马上就是你的新邻居了
In fact, a few of them are your new neighbors.
我的人会来找我的  他们会杀了你
My people will hunt you down. They will kill you.
我们可以做个交易
But we can make a deal.
帮我整垮拉兹拉斯  你想要什么都可以
You help me take down Lazarus, you can set any deal you want.
不  我对目前的生意很满意  多谢
No, I'm good with the deal I got. Thank you.
伊莲娜
Elena.
我得说  你有种
You got balls. I'll give you that.
你不杀我吗
You're not gonna kill me?
他让我来  因为他欠你的
He sent me because he owed you.
他说他想让你活着
He said he wanted you to live.
谁让你来的
Who sent you?
谁想让我活着
Who wanted me to live?
拉兹拉斯
Lazarus.
战术小队在凌晨六点突击了那里
Tactical teams raided the compound at 0600 this morning,
就在你打电话后不久
shortly after your call.
那里已经空了  什么都没了
The place was empty. Everything's gone.
房子属于一个海外公司的
The mansion itself is held in a trust
信托机构
by an offshore corporation.
要花好几个月才能找到真正的主人
It'll be months before we find out who the real owners are.
如果真能找到的话
If ever.
瓦肯·西蒙斯呢
And what about Vulcan Simmons?
我的小队今早在华盛顿高地拘捕了他
My team picked him up this morning in Washington Heights --
那离这儿很远
nowhere near the compound.
他们审了他一个上午  但…
They've been questioning him all the morning, but --
他有不在场证明
He had an alibi for last night.
我们会继续调查他  但是没有任何证据
We'll go after him, but without evidence,
你的一切指控都很难成立
it will difficult to make any of your allegations stick.
你是说我们一无所获吗
Are you saying we have nothing?
不  不是一无所获
No, not nothing.
未来期货
Future Forward?
没错  这是洗钱集团的一部分
Yeah, part of the money-laundering operation --
不管这是个什么
whatever it was,
他们都转了一大笔钱到这个账户上
they are funneling a lot of cash into that account.
你看  我只要一不在你身边就出事了吧
See what happens when I leave you alone?
宝贝  你从来没离开过我
Babe, I wasn't alone.
当他们拷问我的时候
When they were interrogating me,
让我撑下来的唯一动力就是想着你
the only thing that kept me going was thinking about you,
还有我们的未来  我们的婚礼
about our future, the wedding.
你一直都在我身边
You were with me the whole time.
我们也不算是全盘皆输
Well, at least it's not a total loss.
现在警察知道瓦肯·西蒙斯就是拉兹拉斯
Now that the police know that Vulcan Simmons is Lazarus,
他们就会一直留意他的举动
they'll be watching him.
他没机会东山再起了
He will not be able to rebuild his operation.
他不是拉兹拉斯
He's not Lazarus.
如果是他的话  我早就死了
If he was, then I would be dead.
瓦肯·西蒙斯只是个傀儡
Vulcan Simmons is just a figurehead.
幕后黑手另有他人  一个权利更大
Someone else is behind this, someone higher up,
并且想留我一条活路的人
someone who wanted me alive.
谁
Who?
一个势力更大的人
Someone bigger.
这不可能啊
This can't be right.
恐怕事实就是如此  头
I'm afraid it is, sir.
你是说未来期货是个
You're saying that's what Future Forward is --
超级政治行动委员会
a political super pac?
那些黑钱都流向这里了
That's where the money was going?
而且这也是这起案件跟那个差点被杀死的
Yeah, and that's a connection to Evan Potter,
伊万·波特之间的联系
our would-be victim.
波特的客户  富有的对冲基金经理  杰森·克科勒
Potter did all the legal work to establish the super pac
政坛人脉极广  创建了这个超级政治行动委员会
for a client of his -- a wealthy hedge-fund manager
波特帮他做了法律文件
with significant political connections named Jason Kochler.
贩毒的钱被转进
It would appear as if drug money were being funneled
未来期货账户上
into Future Forward's accounts.
过去几个月共入账近一亿六千万美金
Nearly $160 million in the past several months.
接下来这笔钱就通过一个
It was then legally laundered,
匿名的空壳公司和另一个秘密的超级政治委员会
passing through an anonymous shell corp
被合法地洗干净了
and second secret super pac.
什么叫做"合法地洗干净"
What do you mean "legally launded"?
-这笔钱现在去哪了  -不见了
- Where's that money now? - It's gone.
规范这类型超级政治委员会的
Federal tax and banking laws
联邦税收和银行法
that regulate these kind of super pacs
使我们无法查出
make it impossible for us to find out
这笔钱的真实来源和去向
where that money actually came from or went.
肯定有人知道
Well, someone must be able to tell us.
伊万·波特
Evan Potter.
不  他只负责为克科勒成立这个组织
No. He just set up the pac for Kochler.
他不负责运营
He didn't run it.
那我们就得把杰森·克科勒抓来审审
Then we need to bring Jason Kochler in here.
不可能了
We can't.
他今早心脏病去世了
He died of a heart attack this morning.
所以你们才查不到那笔钱的去向
That's why you couldn't find the money.
有人用那笔钱建立了一个巨型政治筹措基金
Someone's using it to build a massive political war chest.
可是谁干的呢
But who?
我们是不可能查到的了
It's impossible to know.
认识我的人都知道
Those of you who know me
我能走到今天这一步全靠
know that I've gotten where I am today
我坚定不渝地完成需要的一切工作
by doing whatever it takes to get the job done.
这才是这个国家所需要的领导才能
That is the kind of leadership this country needs,
也正因这样  我现在正式成立竞选研究委员会
and that is why I am forming an exploratory committee
来筹备竞选美国总统的事宜
for a run for the presidency of the United States.
布莱肯议员  早期的领跑者
Senator Bracken, an early front runner,
据传已经收到了众多大型出资人
is rumored to have significant funding
提供的多笔巨额竞选基金
already lined up from major contributors.
他躲在瓦肯·西蒙斯背后
Hiding behind Vulcan Simmons,
用来路不明的钱资助自己竞选
funding his campaign with dirty money,
扫清一切路上遇到的障碍
killing whoever gets in his way,
就像他杀害我母亲那样
just like he did with my mom.
幕后黑手一定是他
It's him.
而我们却无法证实这一切
And we have no way of proving it.
也许联邦调查局会有所发现
Maybe the feds will find something.
不会的  布莱肯隐藏的太好了
No. Bracken is so well-insulated.
简直堪称是天才
It's genius, actually.
他搞到了自己所需要的所有竞选基金
He has all the campaign funds that he needs
同时不需要欠任何带有个人目的的组织的人情
without having to compromise or be beholden
或是对他们做出任何妥协
to any special-interest groups.
但如果幕后黑手真的是他的话
But if it really was him,
他何不让你葬身在树林里呢
why wouldn't he just let you die in the woods?
他为什么要派伊莲娜去救你呢
Why would he send Elena to save you?
因为我去年破获暗杀行动的时候
Because when I stopped the assassination last year,
救了他一命
I saved him.
他说过他欠我的
And he told me that he owed me.
现在我们两清了
And now we're even.
所以下一次我们再见面的时候
So the next time that we see each other...
上床睡觉吧
Come to bed.